Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the peppermint bark
blizzard. Let me show you how to make
it. First, we need a peppermint flavored
base. So, we're doing 400 g of your
favorite fat-free high protein milk,
some sweetener, salt, zantham gum,
vanilla bean paste, and then an 1/8 of a
teaspoon of peppermint extract. You got
to be super careful with this. Too much
is going to taste like toothpaste. Too
little is going to taste like vanilla
ice cream. And we're going to freeze the
base for at least 16 hours, ideally 24.
Take it out, throw it in your Ninja
Creamy on the light ice cream setting.
While that's running, you can grab your
peppermint bark, chop that up into
whatever size pieces you want, hollow
out a hole in your ice cream, pour in
your peppermint bark, and then run it on
the mixing setting. Then all that's left
to do is enjoy. Comment which blizzard I
should recreate